<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<ds_strings_archive archive_type="1" lang="en" region_id="2">
    <!--=Credits to SuperWorldSun for all strings-->
    <!--=SupersStoryStrings Version-->

    <!--Fishing-->
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="263">{09}</string><!--Bite-->
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="263">{09}</string><!--No Bite-->

    <!--HMs in Unova-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="280">{09}</string> <!--Use Cut?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="280">{09}</string> <!--Cut Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="280">Need HM-Cut!</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="280">{09}</string> <!--Use Strength?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="10" table_id="280">{09}</string> <!--Strength Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="8" table_id="280">Need HM-Strength!</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="13" table_id="280">{09}</string> <!--Use Surf?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="14" table_id="280">{09}</string> <!--Surf Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="23" table_id="280">{09}</string> <!--Use Waterfall?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="24" table_id="280">{09}</string> <!--Waterfall Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="25" table_id="280">Need HM-Waterfall!</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="31" table_id="280">{09}</string> <!--Use Dive?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="32" table_id="280">{09}</string> <!--Dive Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="30" table_id="280">Need HM-Dive!</string>
    <!--These 3 are used in all regions-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="27" table_id="280">{09}</string><!--Flash Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="28" table_id="280">{09}</string><!--Teleport Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="29" table_id="280">{09}</string><!--Dig Used!-->

<!--Npcs-->
    <!--Gyms-->
        <!--Chili Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="11" table_id="12">[$8632]  /  +50%[$12948]  /  +75%[$15106]  /  +100%[$17264]\n \nYeeeeooow!\nTime to play with FIRE!!\nI'm the strongest of us brothers!\n\n</string>
        <!--Chili on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="29" table_id="12">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8632]  /  +50%[$12948]  /  +75%[$15106]  /  +100%[$17264]\n \nChili: Oh! It's you!\nYour fire is more intense than when you got the Trio Badge!</string>

        <!--Cilan Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="12" table_id="12">[$8632]  /  +50%[$12948]  /  +75%[$15106]  /  +100%[$17264]\n \nWhat incredible luck for you--you get to\nbattle the best among the three of us.\n\n</string>
        <!--Cilan on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="28" table_id="12">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8632]  /  +50%[$12948]  /  +75%[$15106]  /  +100%[$17264]\n \nCilan: In the Unova region, um, we are still novice Gym Leaders.\nWhich means, well, that other Gym Leaders are much stronger\nthan we are. Going...slow...and steady...is OK, so... we compete\nwith one another and get, um, stronger and stronger.</string>

        <!--Cress Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="13" table_id="12">[$8632]  /  +50%[$12948]  /  +75%[$15106]  /  +100%[$17264]\n \nSo, um, if you're OK with me, I'll, um, put everything\nI've got into being, er, you know, your opponent.\n\n</string>
        <!--Cress on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="30" table_id="12">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8632]  /  +50%[$12948]  /  +75%[$15106]  /  +100%[$17264]\n \nCress: ...We heard about the incident with N's Castle. If we\nhad received the message in time, the three of us could\nhave helped.</string>

        <!--Lenora Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="24">[$8736]  /  +50%[$13104]  /  +75%[$15288]  /  +100%[$17472]\n \nWelcome! The director of the Nacrene Museum and the\nNacrene Gym's Leader is me! Lenora! Well then, challenger,\nI'm going to research how you battle with the Pokémon\nyou've so lovingly raised!\n\n</string>
        <!--Lenora on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="9" table_id="24">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8736]  /  +50%[$13104]  /  +75%[$15288]  /  +100%[$17472]\n \nLenora: Oh, it's you! As always, you're raising your Pokémon\nwith a lot of love! By the way, ol' Clay contacted me recently.\nHe said you can find Pokémon Fossils in Twist Mountain!\nGo check it out if you like!</string>

        <!--Burgh Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="34">[$8840]  /  +50%[$13260]  /  +75%[$15470]  /  +100%[$17680]\n \nThanks again for your help. My bug Pokémon are scurrying with\nexcitement about getting to battle you. Let's get straight to it!\n\n</string>
        <!--Burgh on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="34">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8840]  /  +50%[$13260]  /  +75%[$15470]  /  +100%[$17680]\n \nBurgh: Heya! This is what I do.\nI keep raising Pokémon and drawing pictures inspired by the\nPokémon I raise. It's what I love to do.\nMy life hums with energy. What could be better?</string>
        <!--Random NPC on button-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="9" table_id="34">Now. Come. On. Step on this switch, and what happens?\nMoi!</string>

        <!--Elesa Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="68">[$8944]  /  +50%[$13416]  /  +75%[$15652]  /  +100%[$17888]\n \nDid the fantastic speed leave you dizzy? My beloved Pokémon\nwill be the next one to make your head spin!\n\n</string>
        <!--Elesa on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="7" table_id="68">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8944]  /  +50%[$13416]  /  +75%[$15652]  /  +100%[$17888]\n \nElesa: I think the real me is the one who battles with Pokémon as\na Gym Leader. A model's job is to make someone else's vision\nlook like a reality. It's interesting, but it's not easy...</string>

        <!--Clay Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="102">[$9048]  /  +50%[$13572]  /  +75%[$15834]  /  +100%[$18096]\n \nWell... Think it's about time to see fer myself what it is about yer\nskills that made a Gym Leader like Elesa take such a shine to ya.\n\n</string>
        <!--Clay on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="102">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9048]  /  +50%[$13572]  /  +75%[$15834]  /  +100%[$18096]\n \nClay: Mrrmph! You, huh? Remember what I done told ya? If ya\nthink ya can go, go wherever, and if ya think ya can do somethin',\nkeep doin' it. Do things how ya want! Decide yer own limits.</string>

        <!--Skyla Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="113">[$9152]  /  +50%[$13728]  /  +75%[$16016]  /  +100%[$18304]\n \nHee-hee! I've been waiting for you.\nDid you enjoy flying with the help of the Mistralton Gym cannons?\nThey're my pride and joy! This time, let's try something else!\n\n</string>
        <!--Skyla on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="113">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9152]  /  +50%[$13728]  /  +75%[$16016]  /  +100%[$18304]\n \nSkyla: Are you and your Pokémon well? Our battle together was\nso much fun. Now, my Pokémon and I have started training again.\nI don't usually let people travel in my cargo plane, but battling\nwith you was such a blast that I'd make an exception.</string>

        <!--Brycen Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="119">[$9256]  /  +50%[$13884]  /  +75%[$16198]  /  +100%[$18512]\n \nYou appear ready to face a Gym Leader. Then... Bring it!\n\n</string>
        <!--Brycen on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="7" table_id="119">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9256]  /  +50%[$13884]  /  +75%[$16198]  /  +100%[$18512]\n \nBrycen: In the past, when I was hurt and depressed, Alder shared\nthis with me... There is strength in being with other people and\nPokémon. Receiving their support makes you stronger. The\nyoung man named Cheren also seems to understand this now.</string>

        <!--Iris Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="126">[$9360]  /  +50%[$14040]  /  +75%[$16380]  /  +100%[$18720]\n \nHi! I'm Iris, the amazingly strong Gym Leader!\nTell me... What Pokémon are you using? How will you fight?\nOoh, I'm super curious, so let's just get started!\n\n</string>
        <!--Iris on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="126">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9360]  /  +50%[$14040]  /  +75%[$16380]  /  +100%[$18720]\n \nYou've been on a journey and seen a lot of the world. I'm like\nthat, too! I'm from way out in the country. I'm really happy that\nI've gotten to meet lots of different people and Pokémon!!</string>

    <!--Elite Four-->
        <!--Door Guard-->

        <!--Statue-->
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="142">Words are engraved on the statue:\n“Four great warriors form this Pokémon League.\nTo the southwest is one who does not fear the Ghost type.\nTo the southeast is one who channels the power of the\nFighting type. To the northwest is one who has mastered the\nDark type. To the northeast is one who knows the mind of the\nPsychic type. If you can defeat these warriors with your\ncourage and wisdom, you shall be led to the summit,\nwhere the strongest Champion awaits."</string>

        <!--Shauntal Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="145">“Eyes brimming with dark flame, this man rejected everything\nother than himself in order to bring about one singular justice..."\nThat's part of a novel I'm writing. I was inspired by the challenger\nwho was just here, and somehow I got a little sad... Excuse me.\nYou're a challenger, right? I'm the Elite Four's Ghost-type\nPokémon user, Shauntal, and I shall be your opponent.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="145">“The Trainer's thoughts joined with the Pokémon's mind, and a\nlustrous Aqua Ring unfurled..." That's part of a novel I wrote.\nI absolutely love writing about the close bonds between the\nTrainers who come here and the Pokémon they train. Could I\nuse you and your Pokémon as a subject?\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="145">“‘Do you know Thunderbolt?' was his first greeting to me.\nIt wasn't until after we battled that I learned his name was Volkner."\n\nThat's part of a novel I wrote.\n\nI absolutely love writing about the close\nbonds between the Trainers who\n\ncome here and the Pokémon they train.\n\nCould I use you and your Pokémon as\na subject?\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="145">“The tiny but strong Pokémon looked up at its Trainer and saw\nthe seeds of doubt taking root as together they faced their\ntoughest opponent yet. The Pokémon sounded a soft cry of\nreassurance, and the battle began..." That was part of a novel\nI wrote. I absolutely love writing about the close bonds between\nthe Trainers who come here and the Pokémon they train.\nCould I use you and your Pokémon as a subject?\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="7" table_id="145">“This world doesn't exist just for you. And I'll tell you why..."\nThat was part of a novel I wrote. I absolutely love writing about\nthe close bonds between the Trainers who come here and the\nPokémon they train. Could I use you and your Pokémon as a\nsubject?\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="8" table_id="145">“I have no idea what day it is today, but I will never forget it\nfor the rest of my life." That was part of a novel I wrote.\nI absolutely love writing about the close bonds between the\nTrainers who come here and the Pokémon they train.\nCould I use you and your Pokémon as a subject?\n\n</string>

        <!--Shauntal lost Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="145">S-sorry! First, I must apologize to my Pokémon... I'm really sorry\nyou had a bad experience because of me! Oh! It's not your fault!\nThis is how battles always are. Even in light of that, I'm still one\nof the Elite Four!</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="9" table_id="145">S-sorry! First, I must apologize to my Pokémon... I'm really sorry\nyou had a bad experience because of me! Oh! It's not your fault!\nThis is how battles always are. Even in light of that, I'm still one\nof the Elite Four!</string>
        <!-- Shauntal Post Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="145">Every person who works with Pokémon has a Pokémon story to\ntell. I've found that stories where people and Pokémon help each\nother out are far more interesting than stories about only people,\nor only Pokémon!</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="10" table_id="145">Every person who works with Pokémon has a Pokémon story to\ntell. I've found that stories where people and Pokémon help each\nother out are far more interesting than stories about only people,\nor only Pokémon!</string>
        <!-- Shauntal Post Battle (All Beaten)-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="11" table_id="145">Challenger, if you defeat the entire Elite Four of the Pokémon\nLeague, you can go on to challenge the Champion. And you\nhave earned that right. Your story is yours and yours alone.\nPlease weave a wonderful tale!</string>

        <!--Grimsley Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="146">Man oh man... What is going on today?Challengers coming one right\nafter another. Well, no matter. I am Grimsley of the Elite Four, and I will\nfulfill my duty to be your opponent.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="146">Life is a serious battle, and you have to use the tools you're given.\nIt's more important to master the cards you're holding than to\ncomplain about the ones your opponents were dealt. Let us\nbegin. And may the best Trainer win! Contests like this are\nproof that you are really living...\n\n</string>
        <!--Grimsley lost Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="146">Whether or not you get to fight at full strength, whether or not luck smiles\non you--none of that matters. Only results matter. And a loss is a loss.\nSee, victory shines like a bright light. And right now, you and your Pokémon\nare shining brilliantly.</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="146">There are bad ways to win-- and good ways to lose. What's\ninteresting and troubling is that it's not always clear which\nis which. A flipped coin doesn't always land heads or tails.\nSometimes it may never land at all...</string>
        <!--Grimsley Post Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="146">Excellent! The nice thing about Pokémon battles is they teach\nthe loser something, as well. That said... You should take that\nstrength and test it against the rest of the Elite Four!</string>
        <!--Grimsley Post Battle (All Beaten)-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="7" table_id="146">Astonishing! You have defeated every member of the Pokémon\nLeague's Elite Four. But it isn't over yet. There is one more\nopponent against whom you must prove your strength. Check\nthe statue in the central plaza, and continue to the final room.</string>

        <!--Caitlin Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="148">Who are you? How impudent you are to disturb my sleep. Hmf...\nYou appear to possess a combination of strength and kindness.\nVery well. Make your best effort not to bore me with a\nyawn-inducing battle. Clear?\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="148">Who's there? Who is so uncouth as to disturb my sleep? Hmf... It's\nyou again. Still, you possess that combination of kindness and\nstrength. Yet you seem stronger than before... Do be sure not to\nbore me with a snooze-inducing battle, is that clear?\n\n</string>
        <!--Caitlin lost Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="148">You haven't faced all of the members of the Elite Four yet, have you?\nDon't concern yourself about me. Go on ahead.</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="148">Alas! Even with the knowledge and skill passed down in my\nfamily of Trainers, I still can't win. The reason I came\nhere in the first place was to encounter Trainers like you...</string>
        <!--Caitlin Post Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="148">In the past, when I battled, the force of my emotions shook me greatly.\nWhen my power awoke, I came close to destroying everything around me.\nThat weak person no longer exists... Still, sometimes, my determination fails.\nAlways, I aspire to wrap up a victory with elegance and grace. I invite you\nto be my opponent again in the future, if you wish.</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="148">In the past, my untrained heart made my power run wild.\nI was forbidden to battle. All I craved then was to experience\nthe pure excitement of battling like this. Hee hee...\nAlthough I'm embarrassed, I can't help smiling right now.</string>
        <!--Caitlin Post Battle (All Beaten)-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="7" table_id="148">You have defeated the Pokémon League's Elite Four.\nYou have earned the right to proceed to the Champion's room.\nMaking an entrance is not the point. Once you're there, you'll\nneed to unleash your power to the fullest!</string>

        <!--Marshal Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="147">Greetings, challenger. My name is Marshal.\nIn order to master the art of fighting, I'm training under my mentor,\nAlder. My mentor sees your potential as a Trainer and is taking an\ninterest in you. It is my intention to test you--to take you to the\nlimits of your strength. Kiai!\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="147">I thank you deeply for the chance for another round of combat\nagainst you. In myself, I seek to develop the strength of a fighter.\nAnd shatter any weakness in myself! Prevailing with the force of\nmy convictions! Victory, decisive victory, is my intention!\nChallenger, here I come!\n\n</string>
        <!--Marshal lost Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="147">There are still many strong Trainersin this Pokémon League.\nYou should deepen your bonds with your Pokémon by battling with them.</string>
        <!--Marshal Post Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="147">In times past, I wandered all the regions of the world in pursuit\nof strength... One day, I met my mentor and began to grasp the\nwisdom of making strength an internal quality... And one day,\nI decided to become part of the Elite Four of Unova... For some\nreason, the battle we just had brought those fateful times\nback to mind.</string>
        <!--Marshal Post Battle (All Beaten)-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="147">Now... You have become the strongest Trainer in this Pokémon League.\nThe statue in the central chamber will take you to the Champion's room.\nWe, the Elite Four of Unova, are sworn to follow the Champion's order\nto be neutral. So the rest is up to you!</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="7" table_id="147">The strength shown by you and your Pokémon has deeply\nimpressed me... Please, continue to the next room to face\nthe strongest Trainer of the Unova region!</string>

        <!--Alder Battle (1st rematch)-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="22" table_id="149">Alder: I am grateful for what you did about N. I don't\nknow what he's thinking now, but I'm sure he realizes that\ndifferent people and Pokémon have their own paths to follow.\nSay now, how about a match with the strongest Trainer in the Unova region?\n\n</string>
        <!--Alder Battle (2nd+ rematch)-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="23" table_id="149">Alder: I've really been looking forward\nto deciding who's the strongest\nPokémon Trainer in the Unova region! Kiai!\n\n</string>
        <!--Alder End Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="24" table_id="149">Alder: Well done! You certainly are an unmatched talent!\nCome with me!\n\n</string>
        <!--Alder Hall of fame 1st time-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="150">Alder: This room is the Hall of Fame. It exists to commemorate\nthe Trainers and Pokémon who have demonstrated their stellar\nstrength and kindness of heart.\n\n</string>
        <!--Alder Hall of fame 2nd+-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="150">Alder: No matter how many times I visit,\nI always feel a little awed by the names engraved here.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="150">Well, now, {00}.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="150">Well, now, {00}.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="150">With your skill and persistence, you have earned your place\nin this Hall of Fame. Your name, the account of your journey,\nand the history of your battles will all be recorded here.\nI hope all of this becomes a support to you and helps you\ngrow stronger. Now, Trainer, you and the Pokémon who\nfought by your side will be recorded in this machine!\n\n</string>

        <!--first time walking into Cnythias house-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="456">???: What's this?\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="456">What an uncanny resemblance... It's surprising to meet another\nTrainer who has intense eyes like that Pokémon Trainer.\nWhat's your name? ... OK. I'll remember that! {00},\nnice to meet you. I'm Cynthia. I'm a Pokémon Trainer,\ntoo, like you. I have an insatiable curiosity for\nresearching Pokémon myths.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="456">I'm sure you know about Undella Town's Abyssal Ruins, right?\nI'm staying here at my friend's villa so I can investigate them.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="456">In order to get to know each other better as Pokémon Trainers,\nI would like our Pokémon to have a match.\nWould you care to be my opponent?</string>
        <!--Cnythia say yes-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="456">Before I send out my Pokémon, my heart always begins to race...\nInteresting... My Pokémon in their Poké Balls are radiating a\nhappy feeling. Are you the reason? What are you?\n\n</string>
        <!--Cnythia say no-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="456">Ha ha. You prefer to take things slowly and rationally,\nam I right? When you're ready, come and talk to me.\nI'll be happy to see you.</string>
        <!--come back before first fight-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="456">Cynthia: Oh. You've had a chance to get ready?\nI do want our Pokémon to have a match...\nAre you prepared to be my opponent?</string>
        <!--win first fight-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="7" table_id="456">Cynthia: That was beyond my expectation! What an exceptional\nbattle! You certainly bear a resemblance to that Trainer\nwho faced Giratina... Oh, pardon me. I was just thinking\nout loud. I love being here in spring and summer.\nI can't stay all year, because there's so much to investigate\nin Sinnoh, as well. You're a great Trainer, and it would make\nme happy to see you again sometime.</string>
        <!--first cool down-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="8" table_id="456">Cynthia: I love to come here in spring and summer.\nBut there are a lot of things to investigate in Sinnoh, as well.\nI'd be delighted to see you again.\nYou're an awesome Pokémon Trainer!</string>


        <!--Cnythia Rematches-->
        <!--Cnythia interaction-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="9" table_id="456">[$16560]  /  +50%[$24840]  /  +75%[$28980]  /  +100%[$33120]\n \nCynthia: How terrific to see you again! I've got to tell you...\nMy Pokémon are excited to battle yours.\nWould you care to be my opponent?</string>
        <!--Cnythia say yes-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="10" table_id="456">Cynthia: This will be such fun! No holds barred!\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="15" table_id="456">Cynthia: As our Pokémon meet in battle, I'll learn more\nabout you and how you've taken care of them.\n\n</string>

        <!--Cnythia say no-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="11" table_id="456">Cynthia: Oh, what a pity. Summers in Undella Town make me\nfeel like I'm on holiday. I forget about battling! But in spring,\nI feel like getting worked up with a good battle.</string>
        <!--Cnythia say no-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="16" table_id="456">Cynthia: I'm a little disappointed.I know you can battle on bigger\nstages than you've done so far! It's so plain to me that your light\ncan shine brighter than this...</string>

        <!--Cnythia Lost-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="18" table_id="456">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$16560]  /  +50%[$24840]  /  +75%[$28980]  /  +100%[$33120]\n \nCynthia: When you meet Trainers, battle them to learn about the\nkind of people they are. Observe the Pokémon they choose, which\nmoves they taught them, and which items the Pokémon hold.\nYou don't need words at such times...\nIf you want to know more about me...\nCome to Sinnoh!</string>
        <!--Cnythia cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="13" table_id="456">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$16560]  /  +50%[$24840]  /  +75%[$28980]  /  +100%[$33120]\n \nCynthia: For some reason, this reminds me of a time when\nI told a Trainer like you to go see many, many more places\nand to meet many more Pokémon. For me, it has really\nbeen worthwhile to come all the way to far Unova. Why?\nBecause... I met you, and my world got wider!</string>



    <!--Morimoto interact-->
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="9" table_id="53">[$15660]  /  +50%[$23490]  /  +75%[27405]  /  +100%[31320]\n \nOh! You've become strong! I can tell.\nDo you want to have a battle with me?</string>
    <!--Morimoto say yes-->
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="10" table_id="53">Well, let's begin!\n\n</string>
    <!--Morimoto say no-->
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="12" table_id="53">No? I've been raising Pokémon, thinking about their Abilities\nand just the right combination of held items. What a pity...\n</string>
    <!--Morimoto Lost/cooldown-->
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="11" table_id="53">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$15660]  /  +50%[$23490]  /  +75%[27405]  /  +100%[31320]\n \nYou think about battles very thoroughly.\nI lost, but I learned a lot from you.\nBesides, it was fun! Come back again tomorrow.</string>

    <!--Nurse Joy-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="346">{09}</string> <!--Morning Healing from NJ-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="346">{09}</string>

    <!--Healing from NJ-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="346">{09}</string>

    <!--saying no...-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="8" table_id="346">{09}</string>

    <!--Waiting...-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="346">{09}</string>

    <!--Thanks for waiting-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="7" table_id="346">{09}</string>

    <!--After Heal-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="8" table_id="346">{09}</string>

    <!--Shop Npcs-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="424">{09}</string> <!--Shop Npc greeting-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="424">{09}</string> <!--Shop TM Npc-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="424">{09}</string> <!--Shop Npc goodbye-->

    <!--Funny Walking npc Text-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="27" table_id="159">I got a 0 Phase Zorua</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="28" table_id="159">Do you not know how PokeMMO works? Please do not argue with me.</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="29" table_id="159">Do people really Masterball Alphas?</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="30" table_id="159">I got my first shiny, Tentacruel!</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="31" table_id="159">When is the next event?</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="32" table_id="159">I swear im Shiny locked</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="33" table_id="159">I'm 200k Dry</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="34" table_id="159">Trubbish is my favorite Pokemon!</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="35" table_id="159">Whats an easy money making method?</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="36" table_id="159">Nah, i'd Win.</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="37" table_id="159">Where to get the bike in Kanto</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="38" table_id="159">I need these Pheno Pokemon to finish my pokedex, they're impossible to find!!!</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="39" table_id="159">Can anyone help me beat E4</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="40" table_id="159">252+ SpA Choice Specs Kyogre Water Spout (150 BP) vs. 0 HP / 0- SpD Your Argument in Rain: 594-698 (173.1 - 203.4%) -- guaranteed OHKO</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="41" table_id="159">Can someone price check my pokemon?</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="42" table_id="159">[this message has been deleted by a mod]</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="43" table_id="159">Gen 6 When?</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="44" table_id="159">WOW, SupersStrings is awesome!</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="45" table_id="159">Hey guys, did you know that in terms of human companionship, Flareon is objectively the most huggable Pokemon? While their maximum temperature is likely too much for most, they are capable of controlling it, so they can set themselves to the perfect temperature for you. Along with that, they have a lot of fluff, making them undeniably incredibly soft to touch. But that's not all, they have a very respectable special defense stat of 110, which means that they are likely very calm and resistant to emotional damage. Because of this, if you have a bad day, you can vent to it while hugging it, and it won't mind. It can make itself even more endearing with moves like Charm and Baby Doll Eyes, ensuring that you never have a prolonged bout of depression ever again.</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="46" table_id="159">I Masterballed an Alpha</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="47" table_id="159">Can someone give me a Pokemon?</string>

</ds_strings_archive>