<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<strings is_override="0" is_primary="0" lang="en">
    <!--=Credits to SuperWorldSun for all strings-->
    <!--=SupersStoryStrings Version-->

<!--Npc-->
    <!--Gym-->
        <!--Brock Battle-->
            <string id="1641684">[$8632]  /  +50%[$12948]  /  +75%[$15106]  /  +100%[$17264]\n \nSo, you're here. I'm BROCK. I'm PEWTER's GYM LEADER.\nMy rock-hard willpower is evident even in my POKéMON.\nMy POKéMON are all rock hard, and have true-grit determination.\nThat's right - my POKéMON are all the ROCK type! Fuhaha!\nYou're going to challenge me knowing that you'll lose?\nThat's the TRAINER's honor that compels you to challenge me.\nFine, then! Show me your best!</string>
        <!--Brock End Battle-->
            <string id="1642063">\n\n</string>
        <!--Brock on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1642767">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8632]  /  +50%[$12948]  /  +75%[$15106]  /  +100%[$17264]\n \nThere are all kinds of TRAINERS in this huge world of ours.\nYou appear to be very gifted as a POKéMON TRAINER.\nSo let me make a suggestion.\nGo to the GYM in CERULEAN and test your abilities.</string>

        <!--Misty Battle-->
            <string id="1647087">[$8736]  /  +50%[$13104]  /  +75%[$15288]  /  +100%[$17472]\n \nHi, you're a new face! Only those TRAINERS who have a policy\nabout POKéMON can turn pro. What is your approach when you\ncatch and train POKéMON? My policy is an all-out offensive\nwith WATER-type POKéMON!</string>
        <!--Misty End Battle-->
            <string id="1647661">\n\n</string>
        <!--Misty on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1647295">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8736]  /  +50%[$13104]  /  +75%[$15288]  /  +100%[$17472]\n \nTM03 teaches WATER PULSE. Use it on an aquatic POKéMON!</string>

        <!--Lt. Surge Battle-->
            <string id="1657764">[$8840]  /  +50%[$13260]  /  +75%[$15470]  /  +100%[$17680]\n \nHey, kid! What do you think you're doing here? You won't live\nlong in combat! Not with your puny power! I tell you, kid,\nelectric POKéMON saved me during the war! They zapped my\nenemies into paralysis! The same as I'll do to you!</string>
        <!--Lt. Surge End Battle-->
            <string id="1658371">\n\n</string>
        <!--Lt. Surge on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1657998">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8840]  /  +50%[$13260]  /  +75%[$15470]  /  +100%[$17680]\n \nA little word of advice, kid! Electricity is sure powerful!\nBut, it's useless against GROUND-type POKéMON!</string>

        <!--Erika Battle-->
            <string id="1667348">[$8944]  /  +50%[$13416]  /  +75%[$15652]  /  +100%[$17888]\n \nHello... Lovely weather, isn't it? it's so pleasant......Oh,\ndear... I must have dozed off. Welcome. My name is ERIKA. I am\nthe LEADER of CELADON GYM. I am a student of the art of\nflower arranging. My POKéMON are solely of the GRASS type....\nOh, I'm sorry, I had no idea that you wished to challenge me.\nVery well, but I shall not lose.</string>
        <!--Erika End Battle-->
            <string id="1667680">\n\n</string>
        <!--Erika on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1667768">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8944]  /  +50%[$13416]  /  +75%[$15652]  /  +100%[$17888]\n \nYou are cataloging POKéMON? I must say I'm impressed.\nI would never collect POKéMON if they were unattractive.</string>

        <!--Sabrina Battle-->
            <string id="1684796">[$9152]  /  +50%[$13728]  /  +75%[$16016]  /  +100%[$18304]\n \nI had a vision of your arrival. I have had psychic powers since\nI was a child. It started when a spoon I carelessly tossed, bent.\nI dislike battling, but if you wish, I will show you my powers!</string>
        <!--Sabrina End Battle-->
            <string id="1684994">\n\n</string>
        <!--Sabrina on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1685490">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9152]  /  +50%[$13728]  /  +75%[$16016]  /  +100%[$18304]\n \nTM04 is CALM MIND. It makes the POKéMON concentrate\nto raise both SP. ATK and SP. DEF.</string>

        <!--Koga Battle-->
            <string id="1671982">[$9048]  /  +50%[$13572]  /  +75%[$15834]  /  +100%[$18096]\n \nFwahahaha! A mere child like you dares to challenge me?\nThe very idea makes me shiver with mirth! Very well, I shall\nshow you true terror as a ninja master. Poison brings steady\ndoom. Sleep renders foes helpless. Despair to the creeping\nhorror of POISON-type POKéMON!</string>
        <!--Koga End Battle-->
            <string id="1672260">\n\n</string>
        <!--Koga on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1672321">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9048]  /  +50%[$13572]  /  +75%[$15834]  /  +100%[$18096]\n \nWhen afflicted by TOXIC, a POKéMON suffers more and more.\nIt suffers worsening damage as the battle wears on!\nIt will surely terrorize foes!</string>

        <!--Blaine Battle-->
            <string id="1676611">[$9256]  /  +50%[$13884]  /  +75%[$16198]  /  +100%[$18512]\n \nHah! I am BLAINE, the red-hot LEADER of CINNABAR GYM!\nMy fiery POKéMON are all rough and ready with intense heat!\nThey incinerate all challengers! Hah! You better have BURN HEAL!</string>
        <!--Blaine End Battle-->
            <string id="1676794">\n\n</string>
        <!--Blaine on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1677085">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9256]  /  +50%[$13884]  /  +75%[$16198]  /  +100%[$18512]\n \nTM38 contains FIRE BLAST. Teach it to FIRE-type POKéMON.\nVULPIX or CHARMELEON would be ideal for that move.</string>

    <!--Elite Four-->
        <!-- Door Guard-->
            <string id="1681624">From here on, you face the ELITE FOUR one by one.\nIf you win, a door opens to the next TRAINER. Good luck!</string>
        <!--Lorelei Battle-->
            <string id="1540233">Welcome to the POKéMON LEAGUE. I, LORELEI of the ELITE FOUR,\nhave returned! You know how it goes. No one can best me when\nit comes to icy POKéMON. Freezing moves are powerful. Your\nPOKéMON will be at my mercy when they are frozen solid.\nHahaha! Are you ready?</string>
        <!--Lorelei End Battle-->
            <string id="1540497">\n\n</string>
        <!--Lorelei on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1540528">You're better than I thought. Go on ahead.\nYou only got a taste of the POKéMON LEAGUE's power.</string>

        <!--Bruno Battle-->
            <string id="1540623">I am BRUNO of the ELITE FOUR! Through rigorous training, people\nand POKéMON can become stronger without limit. I've lived and\ntrained with my fighting POKéMON! And that will never change!\n{01}! We will grind you down with our\nsuperior power! Hoo hah!</string>
        <!--Bruno End Battle-->
            <string id="1541129">\n\n</string>
        <!--Bruno on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1541152">My job is done.\nGo face your next challenge.</string>

        <!--Agatha Battle-->
            <string id="1541197">I am AGATHA of the ELITE FOUR. I hear OAK's taken a lot\nof interest in you, child. That old duff was once tough and\nhandsome. But that was decades ago. He's a shadow of his\nformer self. Now he just wants to fiddle with his POKéDEX.\nHe's wrong. POKéMON are for battling! {01}!\nI'll show you how a real TRAINER battles!</string>
        <!--Agatha End Battle-->
            <string id="1541847">\n\n</string>
        <!--Agatha on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1541888">You win! I see what the old duff sees in you now.\nI have nothing else to say. Run along now, child!</string>

        <!--Lance Battle-->
            <string id="1542333">Ah! So, you've returned, {01}! I lead\nthe ELITE FOUR. You can call me LANCE the dragon TRAINER.\nYou know that dragons are mythical POKéMON. They're hard to\ncatch and raise, but their powers are superior. They're virtually\nindestructible. There's no being clever with them. Well, are you\nready to lose? Your LEAGUE challenge ends with me,\n{01}!</string>
        <!--Lance End Battle-->
            <string id="1542677">\n\n</string>
        <!--Lance on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1542738">I still can't believe my dragons lost to you, {01}.\nYou are now the POKéMON LEAGUE CHAMPION! ...Or, you would\nhave been, but you have one more challenge left. There is one\nmore TRAINER to face! His name is...{06}! He beat the ELITE\nFOUR before you. He is the real POKéMON LEAGUE CHAMPION.</string>

        <!--Gary Battle-->
            <string id="1543380">{06}: Hey, {01}!\nYou came back, {01}! Hahah, that is so great!\nMy rival should be strong to keep me sharp. While working on\nmy POKéDEX, I looked all over for POKéMON. Not only that,\nI assembled teams that would beat any POKéMON type.\nAnd now... I'm the POKéMON LEAGUE CHAMPION!\n{01}! Do you know what that means?\nI'll tell you. I am the most powerful TRAINER in the world!</string>
        <!--Gary End Battle-->
            <string id="1543743">\n\n</string>
        <!--Gary on Cooldown-->
            <string id="1543983">Why? Why did I lose? I never made any mistakes raising my\nPOKéMON... Darn it! You're the new POKéMON LEAGUE\nCHAMPION! Although I don't like to admit it...</string>
        <!--Oak saying hi-->
            <string id="1544134">OAK: {01}!</string>
            <string id="1544143">OAK: So, you've won! Sincerely, congratulations! You're\nthe new POKéMON LEAGUE CHAMPION! You've grown up so much\nsince you first left with {02} to work on the POKéDEX.\n{01}, you have come of age!</string>
            <string id="1544335">OAK: {06}... I'm disappointed in you. I came when I heard you'd\nbeaten the ELITE FOUR. But, when I got here, you had already\nlost! {06}, do you understand why you lost? You have forgotten\nto treat your POKéMON with love and trust. Without them,\nyou will never become a CHAMP again!</string>
            <string id="1544611">OAK: {01}.\nYou understand that your victory was not just your own doing.\nThe bond you share with your POKéMON is marvelous.\n{01}! Come with me!</string>
            <string id="1544751">OAK: Er-hem! Congratulations, {01}!\nThis floor is the POKéMON HALL OF FAME. POKéMON LEAGUE\nCHAMPIONS are honored for their exploits here. Their POKéMON\nare also recorded in the HALL OF FAME. {01}!\nYou have worked hard to become the new LEAGUE CHAMPION.\nCongratulations, {01},\nyou and your POKéMON are HALL OF FAMERS!</string>

        <!--Nurse Joy-->
            <!--Healing from NJ-->
                <string id="1725571">{09}</string>
            <!--Waiting...-->
                <string id="1725665">{09}</string>
            <!--Thanks for waiting-->
                <string id="1725739">{09}</string>
            <!--Come back-->
                <string id="1725713">{09}</string>

        <!--Shop Npc-->
            <string id="1729041">{09}</string>
            <string id="1724816">{09}</string>

        <!--DayCare Man (Route 5)-->
            <string id="1695078">I run the DAY-CARE service.\nWould you like me to raise one of your POKéMON?</string>
            <string id="1695292">You're back already? Your {02} needs to\nspend some more time with me.</string>
            <string id="1695360">You owe me ${03} for the return\nof this POKéMON.</string>
            <string id="1695407">Thank you! Here's your POKéMON.</string>
            <string id="1695439">{01} got {02}\nback from the DAY-CARE MAN.</string>
            <string id="1695477">Oh? You only have one POKéMON with you.</string>

        <!--DayCare Lady (Four Island)-->
            <string id="1832932">I'm the DAY-CARE LADY. We can raise POKéMON for you.\nWould you like us to raise one?</string>
            <string id="1833056">Fine, we'll raise your {02} for a while.\nCome back for it later.</string>
            <string id="1695225">Fine, I'll look after your {02} for a while.</string>
            <string id="1833119">We can raise two of your POKéMON.\nWould you like us to raise one more POKéMON for you?</string>
            <string id="1695268">Come see me in a while.</string>
            <string id="1833352">Ah, it's you! Good to see you.\nYour POKéMON can only be doing good!</string>
            <string id="1833420">By level, your {02} has grown by {03}.</string>
            <string id="1833455">Your POKéMON party is full.\nMake room, then come see me.</string>
            <string id="1833531">If you want your {02} back, it will cost ${03}.</string>
            <string id="1833575">Perfect! Here's your POKéMON.</string>
            <string id="1833605">{01} took back {02} from\nthe DAY-CARE LADY.</string>
            <string id="1833704">Will you take your POKéMON back?</string>
            <string id="1833295">Will you take back the other one, too?</string>
        <!--Breeder-->
            <string id="1695517">If you leave me that POKéMON, what will you battle with?</string>

        <!--Breeder & DayCares end text-->
            <string id="1695196">Fine. Come anytime you like.</string>

    <!--Safari-->
        <!--Left clerk-->
            <string id="1670832">Hi! Is it your first time here at the SAFARI ZONE?</string>
            <string id="1670883">The SAFARI ZONE actually has four zones in it. Each zone has\ndifferent kinds of POKéMON, even some rare ones. Use the\nsupplied SAFARI BALLS to catch them. You can also throw\nBAIT or ROCKS besides the SAFARI BALLS. If you throw BAIT,\nthe POKéMON becomes less likely to flee, but harder to catch.\nIf you throw ROCKS, the POKéMON becomes more likely to flee,\nbut easier to catch. When you run out of time or SAFARI BALLS,\nit's game over for you!</string>
        <!--Right clerk-->
            <string id="1670251">Welcome to the SAFARI ZONE!</string>
            <string id="1670279">For just $500, you can play the SAFARI GAME.\nYou can roam the wide-open safari and catch what you like.\nWould you like to play?</string>
            <string id="1670407">That'll be $500, please!\nWe only use a special kind of POKé BALLS here.</string>
            <string id="1670480">{01} received 30 SAFARI BALLS\nfrom the attendant.</string>
            <string id="1670528">We'll call you on the PA when you run out of time\nor SAFARI BALLS. Well, I'll wish you the best of luck!</string>
            <string id="1670633">Okay. Please come again!</string>
        <!--PA Announcement-->
        <string id="1834011">PA: Ding-dong! Time's up!\nPA: Your SAFARI GAME is over!</string>
        <string id="1834067">PA: Ding-dong!\nYou are out of SAFARI BALLS!\nPA: Your SAFARI GAME is over!</string>


    <!--Celadon-->
        <!--Celadon Dept Store-->
            <!--F1 Clerk-->
                <string id="1660125">Hello! Welcome to CELADON DEPT. STORE.\nThe board on the right describes the store layout.</string>
            <!--F1 Counter Sign-->
                <string id="1660215">1F: SERVICE COUNTER\n2F: TRAINER'S MARKET\n3F: TV GAME SHOP\n4F: WISE MAN GIFTS\n5F: DRUGSTORE\nROOFTOP SQUARE: VENDING MACHINES</string>
            <!--Rocket Game Corner-->
                <string id="1666780">Hey! A switch behind the poster!?\nLet's push it!</string>
                <string id="1665344">Welcome!\nYou can exchange your COINS for fabulous prizes next door.</string>
                <string id="1665412">Welcome to ROCKET GAME CORNER!\nDo you need some game COINS?\nWould you like to buy some?</string>
                <string id="1665500">No? Please come play sometime!</string>

    <!--Trainers-->
        <!--Five Island-->
            <!--Resort Gorgeous-->
                <!--PAINTER RAYNA-->
                    <string id="1850480">[$960]  /  +50%[$1440]  /  +75%[$1680]  /  +100%[$1920]\n \nI haven't made any progress...\nI still can't get the right angle...</string>
                    <string id="1615189">[ON COOLDOWN / 6 Hours]\n[$960]   /   +50%[$1440]   /   +75%[$1680]   /   +100%[$1920]\n \nThe sky and the sea... They are so fickle.\nTheir changing expressions make them difficult to capture.</string>
                <!--LADY JACK-->
                    <string id="1850544">[$4012]  /  +50%[$6018]  /  +75%[$7021]  /  +100%[$8024]\n \nOh, you will give me another\nopportunity to match wits with you?</string>
                    <string id="1615361">[ON COOLDOWN / 6 Hours]\n[$4012]  /  +50%[$6018]  /  +75%[$7021]  /  +100%[$8024]\n \nI find it pleasurable to leisurely battle in the gentle sea breeze.</string>
                <!--PAINTER CELINA-->
                    <string id="1850408">[$960]  /  +50%[$1440]  /  +75%[$1680]  /  +100%[$1920]\n \nMust I repeat myself?\nI'm trying to paint.\nPlease keep out of my sight!</string>
                    <string id="1615046">[ON COOLDOWN / 6 Hours]\n[$960]  /  +50%[$1440]  /  +75%[$1680]  /  +100%[$1920]\n \nGILLIAN?\nPlease tilt your head slightly... There! That's the look I want!</string>
                <!--LADY GILLIAN-->
                    <string id="1850609">[$4080]  /  +50%[$6120]  /  +75%[$7140]  /  +100%[$8160]\n \nThey're almost finished making the pool for my POKéMON.\nYou must drop in for a visit.</string>
                    <string id="1615513">[ON COOLDOWN / 6 Hours]\n[$4080]  /  +50%[$6120]  /  +75%[$1680]  /  +100%[$1920]\n \nA pool would be nice, but I must say, a sun-room may be sublime.</string>
                <!--PAINTER DAISY-->
                    <string id="1850358">[$960]  /  +50%[$1440]  /  +75%[$1680]  /  +100%[$1920]\n \nWith these hands, I will create\nmy victory today.</string>
                    <string id="1614896">[ON COOLDOWN / 6 Hours]\n[$960]  /  +50%[$1440]  /  +75%[$1680]  /  +100%[$1920]\n \nUh-oh, my paint tubes have scattered everywhere!</string>
                <!--YOUNGSTER DESTIN-->
                    <string id="1850695">[$928]  /  +50%[$1392]  /  +75%[$1624]  /  +100%[$1856]\n \nI'm a good runner.\nI've gotten even faster!</string>
                    <string id="1615637">[ON COOLDOWN / 6 Hours]\n[$928]  /  +50%[$1392]  /  +75%[$1624]  /  +100%[$1856]\n \nWhen I run with the wind, it feels like I could fly!</string>


    <!--HMs in Kanto-->
    <string id="1725806">{09}</string> <!--Use Surf?-->
    <string id="1725861">{09}</string> <!--Surf Used!-->
    <string id="1826708">{09}</string> <!--Use Cut?-->
    <string id="1826775">{09}</string> <!--Cut Used!-->
    <string id="1826787">Need HM-Cut!</string>
    <string id="1826973">{09}</string> <!--Use Rock Smash?-->
    <string id="1827042">{09}</string> <!--Rock Smash Used!-->
    <string id="1827226">{09}</string> <!--Use Strength?-->
    <string id="1827322">{09}</string> <!--Strength Used!-->
    <string id="1827396">Need HM-Strength!</string>
    <string id="1827460">{09}</string> <!--You can push boulders around-->

</strings>