<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<ds_strings_archive archive_type="0" lang="en" region_id="3">
    <!--=Credits to SuperWorldSun for all strings-->
    <!--=SupersStoryStrings Version-->

    <!--HMs in Sinnoh-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="12" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Use Surf?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="13" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Surf Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Use Cut?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Cut Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="381">Need HM-Cut!</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Use Rock Smash?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Rock Smash Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="381">Need HM-Rock Smash!</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Use Strength?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="10" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Strength Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="11" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Strength Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="9" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--You can push boulders around-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="22" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Use Waterfall?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="23" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Waterfall Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="24" table_id="381">Need HM-Waterfall!</string>
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="18" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Use Rock Climb?-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="19" table_id="381">{09}</string> <!--Rock Climb Used!-->
    <string block_id="0" entry_id="20" table_id="381">Need HM-Rock Climb!</string>

<!--Npcs-->
    <!--Gym-->
        <!--Roark-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="67">[$8632]  /  +50%[$12948]  /  +75%[$15106]  /  +100%[$17264]\n \nWelcome! This is the Oreburgh Pokémon Gym! I'm Roark,\nthe Gym Leader! I'm but one Trainer who decided to walk\nproudly with Rock-type Pokémon! As the Gym Leader, I\nneed to see your potential as a Trainer. And, I'll need to\nsee the toughness of the Pokémon that battle with you!\n\n</string>
        <!--Roark End Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Roark on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="67">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8632]  /  +50%[$12948]  /  +75%[$15106]  /  +100%[$17264]\n \nIn this region of Sinnoh, there are seven other Gym Leaders.\nI should warn you--they're a lot tougher than I am!</string>

        <!--Gardenia-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="87">[$8736]  /  +50%[$13104]  /  +75%[$15288]  /  +100%[$17472]\n \nYou kept me waiting! I'm Eterna's Gym Leader, Gardenia,\nthe Grass-type master! When I first saw you, I was convinced\nyou'd find your way to me. My hunch was right on the money.\nYou have a winning aura about you. So, anyway, this will be fun.\nLet's have our battle!\n\n</string>
        <!--Gardenia End Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1227" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Gardenia on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="87">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8736]  /  +50%[$13104]  /  +75%[$15288]  /  +100%[$17472]\n \nYup! If there's one thing I can tell about you, it's this! You and\nyour Pokémon are gonna get even tougher, and I mean seriously!</string>

        <!--Fantina-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="109">[$8840]  /  +50%[$13260]  /  +75%[$15470]  /  +100%[$17680]\n \nOhohoho!! Finally, you have arrived!\nSince I came to this country, always I try to learn new things.\nThey hold Contests in this city? I say to myself, enfin, I will excel.\nThat is why I dress this way. C'est une performance!\nAlso, I study Pokémon very much. I have come to be Gym Leader.\nAnd, uh, so it shall be that you challenge me.\nBut I shall win. That is what a Gym Leader does, non?\n\n</string>
        <!--Fantina End Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1290" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Fantina on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="109">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8840]  /  +50%[$13260]  /  +75%[$15470]  /  +100%[$17680]\n \nThree Gym Badges... But you must not forget this.\nThere are many other Trainers. Strong Trainers, too.\nThere are many more in Sinnoh. Have patience!\nYou must become stronger, one at a time.</string>

        <!--Maylene-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="144">[$8944]  /  +50%[$13416]  /  +75%[$15652]  /  +100%[$17888]\n \nHello. I'm pleased to meet you. I'm Maylene, and I'm\nthe Gym Leader. I don't really know what it means to be\nstrong, or how I got to be the Gym Leader. But I will do the\nbest I can as the Gym Leader. I take battling very seriously.\nWhenever you're ready!\n\n</string>
        <!--Maylene End Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1275" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Maylene on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="144">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8944]  /  +50%[$13416]  /  +75%[$15652]  /  +100%[$17888]\n \nGee, I'm hungry... Oh, sorry, it's nothing. I didn't say anything.\n{00}, I can't explain what it means to be strong.\nI don't know how much effort goes into being strong... But\nbeing with Pokémon lets us keep making the effort, doesn't it?</string>

        <!--Crasher Wake-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="133">[$9048]  /  +50%[$13572]  /  +75%[$15834]  /  +100%[$18096]\n \nWelcome! I don't get challenged very often!\nThe glory you are now beholding is the Pastoria Gym Leader!\nThat's right, I'm Crasher Wake! My Pokémon were toughened\nup by stormy white waters! They'll take everything you can\nthrow at them and then pull you under! Victory will be ours!\nCome on, let's get it done!\n\n</string>
        <!--Crasher Wake End Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1242" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Crasher Wake on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="133">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9048]  /  +50%[$13572]  /  +75%[$15834]  /  +100%[$18096]\n \nThe styles of battling and winning are as widely varied as\nTrainers are. Do you want to know how I battle? I battle so\nI can say I had fun at the end, whether I win or lose!</string>

        <!--Byron-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="56">[$9152]  /  +50%[$13728]  /  +75%[$16016]  /  +100%[$18304]\n \nAh! That's Oreburgh's Gym Badge! I see, I see! You've defeated\nmy son. But that's no surprise. He still has much to learn.\nIn place of my son Roark, I, Byron, will take your challenge!\n\n</string>
        <!--Byron End Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1163" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Byron on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="56">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9152]  /  +50%[$13728]  /  +75%[$16016]  /  +100%[$18304]\n \nGwahahahaha! The Sinnoh region is vast! Tough Trainers like you\nand {01} crop up constantly to challenge the old guard! With\nmore young Trainers like my son and you two taking charge, the\nfuture of Pokémon is bright! But I'm not stepping aside just yet!\nI merely need to rededicate myself to training on Iron Island.</string>

        <!--Candice Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="178">[$9256]  /  +50%[$13884]  /  +75%[$16198]  /  +100%[$18512]\n \nYou want to challenge Candice? Sure thing! I was waiting for\nsomeone tough! But I should tell you, I'm tough because I know\nhow to focus. Pokémon, fashion, romance... It's all about focus!\nI'll show you just what I mean. Get ready to lose!\n\n</string>
        <!--Candice End Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1317" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Candice on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="178">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9256]  /  +50%[$13884]  /  +75%[$16198]  /  +100%[$18512]\n \nDo you think I should try to act more like an Ice-type Gym Leader?\nLike, do you think I should be more cool and distant?\nThat sort of thing I have trouble with.</string>

        <!--Volkner Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="165">[$9360]  /  +50%[$14040]  /  +75%[$16380]  /  +100%[$18720]\n \n...All right, challenger. It's not often, but some Trainers\nmanage to come and challenge me. But they've all been boring\nbattles. I didn't break a sweat beating them....Sigh... I'm Volkner,\nthe Gym Leader. They say I'm the top Gym Leader in Sinnoh, but...\nAnyway, I guess we'd better get this done. I hope you're the\nTrainer who'll make me remember how fun it is to battle!\n\n</string>
        <!--Volkner End Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1339" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Volkner on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="165">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9360]  /  +50%[$14040]  /  +75%[$16380]  /  +100%[$18720]\n \nYour next step is the Pokémon League challenge. It's time for\nyou to cross the sea and win your way through the gauntlet that\nis Victory Road. Demonstrate to the Pokémon League your\nmastery of your team. Against you, even the Elite Four will be\npushed to fend off your challenge!</string>

    <!--Elite Four-->
        <!--Door Guard-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="184">You will be facing the Elite Four of the Pokémon League. If you\ncan't beat all four of them in a row, you have to start from the\nfirst one again.</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="184">Very well! Trainer, you've indeed collected all the Gym\nBadges of Sinnoh! Demonstrate the power that brought you\nhere and go for glory!</string>

        <!--Aaron Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="185">Hello! Welcome to the Pokémon League! I'm Aaron of the Elite\nFour. It's good to meet you. Oh, I should explain, I'm a huge fan of\nbug Pokémon. Bug Pokémon are nasty-mean, and yet they're\nbeautiful, too... Would you like to know why I take on challengers\nhere? It's because I want to become perfect, just like my bug\nPokémon! OK! Let me take you on!\n\n</string>
        <!--Aaron lost Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1968" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Aaron end Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="185">I lost with the most beautiful and toughest of the bug Pokémon...\nWe lost because I wasn't good enough... That's it! Back to training\ncamp! Let's hear it for me! No... That was wrong... Anyway...\nGo on to the next room! Three Trainers are waiting for you.\nThey're all tougher than me.</string>
        <!--Aaron Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="185">Go on, go to the next room. I'm going to become a top-level\nTrainer who can't be outclassed with my beautiful and tough\nbug Pokémon!</string>

        <!--Bertha Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="186">Well, well. You're quite the adorable Trainer, but you've also got\na spine. Ahaha! I'm Bertha. I have a preference for Ground-type\nPokémon. Well, would you show this old lady how much\nyou've learned?\n\n</string>
        <!--Bertha lost Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1970" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Berthaon end Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="186">You're quite something, youngster. I like how you and your\nPokémon earned the win by working as one. That's what makes\nyou so strong. Ahahaha! I think that you can go as far as you want.</string>
        <!--Berthaon Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="186">The Trainer in the next room is a much more formidable\nopponent. You really must have your wits about you.\nHowever, I think you can go as far as you desire. Ahahaha!</string>

        <!--Flint Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="187">I was waiting for you, challenger!\nFlint, the master of the Fire type, is up next! Battles\nare clashes of the burning spirit of Pokémon. Battles aren't\nabout appearances or what's weak or strong. It all comes\ndown to whether the combatants can burn hot or not.\n\n</string>
        <!--Flint lost Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1973" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Flint end Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="187">... ...\n...Whew...\n...Burnt right down to cinders...</string>
        <!--Flint Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="187">... ... ...Keep going... I know your spirit burns hot.\nYour whole team does.</string>

        <!--Lucian Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="188">Ah, you timed your arrival well. I've just finished reading\na book, you see. Allow me to introduce myself. I am Lucian.\nI am a user of the Psychic type. I must say, you've already\nproven yourself to be outstanding by coming this far. They\nsay I am the toughest of the Elite Four. I'm afraid I will have\nto go all out against you to live up to that reputation.\n\n</string>
        <!--Lucian lost Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1975" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Lucian end Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="188">Congratulations. You've now beaten the Elite Four. However,\nthat doesn't mean you're done with the Pokémon League.\nThere remains the Champion. I should warn you--the Champion\nis far stronger than the Elite Four. Now, go on. Step through the\ndoorway to your final battle.</string>
        <!--Lucian on Cooldown-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="188">I'll be reading books until the next challenger arrives.\nThat will calm my nerves, so that I may deal with all situations\nwithout panicking.</string>

        <!--Cynthia Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="189">Cynthia: One look at you tells me many things about you.\nTogether, you and your Pokémon overcame all the challenges you\nfaced, however difficult. It means that you've triumphed over\nany personal weaknesses, too. The power you learned... I can feel\nit from you. That's enough talking. Let's get on with why you're\nhere. I, Cynthia, accept your challenge as the Pokémon League\nChampion! There won't be any letup from me!\n\n</string>
        <!--Cynthia lost Battle-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1978" table_id="617">\n\n</string>
        <!--Cynthia Beat-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="189">Cynthia: That was excellent. Truly, an outstanding battle. You\ngave the support your Pokémon needed to maximize their power.\nAnd you guided them with certainty to secure victory. You have\nboth passion and calculating coolness. Together, you and your\nPokémon can overcome any challenge that may come your way.\nThose are the impressions I got from our battle. I'm glad I got to\ntake part in the crowning of Sinnoh's new Champion!\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="189">Come with me. We'll take the lift.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="190">Cynthia: The room ahead is the Hall of Fame...\n\n</string>
        <!--Rowan-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="190">Rowan: {00}! Your last battle was splendid!\n\n</string>
        <!--Cynthia-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="190">Cynthia: Oh, hello, Professor Rowan.\n\n</string>
        <!--Rowan-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="190">Rowan: Hm! A child I enlisted for my Pokédex project has come\nthis far... It's only natural that I come and witness the child's\ncrowning glory. {00}! I shouldn't call you\na child anymore. You've grown into a real Champion!\n\n</string>
        <!--Cynthia-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="190">Cynthia: Professor, you still enjoy the enthusiasm kids\nbring to your research, don't you?\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="5" table_id="190">{00}, step this way, please.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="7" table_id="190">Professor Rowan, please join us.\n\n</string>
        <!--Rowan-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="191">Rowan: It's been a long while since I last entered this room...\n\n</string>
        <!--Cynthia-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="191">Cynthia: If your last time here was when I became Champion, then yes,\nthat would be quite a long time ago.\n\n</string>
        <!--Rowan-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="191">Rowan: No matter how many times I come here, I always\nfind myself standing up straighter than usual.\n\n</string>
        <!--Cynthia-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="191">Cynthia: It's a natural reaction, Professor. This room is a\nlegacy to the hopes, dreams, and struggles of Pokémon\nand their Trainers to excel.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="191">Cynthia: {00}, welcome to the Hall of Fame.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="6" table_id="191">Your names will be recorded for posterity here.\nWhat you are leaving are the memories of your adventure\nso far. It's time to record your names. You and your Pokémon.\nRemember, your Pokémon are partners that grew with you\nthrough many challenging battles. This machine will make a\npermanent record of your achievement.\n\n</string>

        <!--Nurse Joy-->
            <!--Healing from NJ-->
                <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="213">{09}</string>
                <string block_id="0" entry_id="120" table_id="213">{09}</string>
                <string block_id="0" entry_id="121" table_id="213">{09}</string>
            <!--Waiting...-->
                <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="213">{09}</string>
            <!--Thanks for waiting-->
                <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="213">{09}</string>
            <!--After Heal-->
                <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="213">{09}</string>

        <!--Shop Npcs-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="37" table_id="213">{09}</string> <!--Shop Npc greeting-->

    <!--DayCare Lady-->
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="15" table_id="547">I'm the Day-Care Lady. We can raise Pokémon for you.\nWould you like us to raise your Pokémon?</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="16" table_id="547">Which Pokémon should we raise for you?\n\n</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="17" table_id="547">Fine, we'll raise your {00} for a while.\nCome back for it later.\n\n</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="18" table_id="547">We can raise two of your Pokémon.\nWould you like us to raise another?</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="20" table_id="547">Oh, fine, then. Come again.</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="22" table_id="547">Do you want to take back the other one, too?</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="24" table_id="547">Ah, it's you! Good to see you. Now, about your Pokémon...\n\n</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="25" table_id="547">By level, your {00} has\ngrown by about {01}.\n\n</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="26" table_id="547">Your Pokémon team is full.\nMake room, then come see me.</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="27" table_id="547">Which Pokémon will you take back?</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="28" table_id="547">If you want your {00} back,\nit will cost ${01}.</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="29" table_id="547">Excellent! Here's your Pokémon.\n\n</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="30" table_id="547">{01} took {00} back\nfrom the Day-Care Lady.\n\n</string>
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="31" table_id="547">Oh? But you only have one Pokémon with you.\nYou can't go off without a Pokémon.\nCome back another time.</string>

    <!--DayCare Lady-->
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="33" table_id="547">If you leave me that Pokémon, what are you gonna battle with?\nCome back another time.</string>

    <!--Both breeders-->
        <string block_id="0" entry_id="23" table_id="547">Very good. Come again.</string>

    <!--The Great Marsh (Safari)-->
        <!--Game Clerk-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="136">Welcome to the Great Marsh, the home of Pastoria's\nSafari Game! All you can catch for just $500!\nWould you like to play a Safari Game?</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="136">That will be $500, please.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="136">Here are your Safari Balls.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="136">{00} received 30 Safari Balls.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="136">We'll let you know when your game is over.\nUntil then, enjoy yourself, please!\nOff you go on your wild excursion!\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="10" table_id="136">OK. I'll relieve you of your remaining Safari Balls.\nThank you for playing. We hope to see you again.\n\n</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="9" table_id="136">You still have time left.\nAre you sure you want to exit the Great Marsh?</string>

        <!--Bug catcher at top stairs-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="137">Each Area in the Marsh has different Pokémon depending\non the day. Here is the list of areas and there rotations!\n\nArea 1\n \n-Sunday: Skorupi\n-Monday: Croagunk\n-Tuesday: Croagunk\n-Wednesday: Carnivine\n-Thursday: Croagunk\n-Friday: Skorupi\n-Saturday: Skorupi\n\nArea 2\n \n-Sunday: Skorupi\n-Monday: Skorupi\n-Tuesday: Croagunk\n-Wednesday: Croagunk\n-Thursday: Carnivine\n-Friday: Croagunk\n-Saturday: Skorupi\n\nArea 3\n \n-Sunday: Croagunk\n-Monday: Skorupi\n-Tuesday: Skorupi\n-Wednesday: Croagunk\n-Thursday: Croagunk\n-Friday: Carnivine\n-Saturday: Croagunk\n\nArea 4\n \n-Sunday: Carnivine\n-Monday: Croagunk\n-Tuesday: Skorupi\n-Wednesday: Skorupi\n-Thursday: Croagunk\n-Friday: Croagunk\n-Saturday: Carnivine\n\nArea 5\n \n-Sunday: Croagunk\n-Monday: Carnivine\n-Tuesday: Croagunk\n-Wednesday: Skorupi\n-Thursday: Skorupi\n-Friday: Croagunk\n-Saturday: Croagunk\n\nArea 6\n \n-Sunday: Croagunk\n-Monday: Croagunk\n-Tuesday: Carnivine\n-Wednesday: Croagunk\n-Thursday: Skorupi\n-Friday: Skorupi\n-Saturday: Croagunk</string>
        <!--Stone Signs inside marsh-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="240">Great Marsh Area 1\n \n-Sunday: Skorupi\n-Monday: Croagunk\n-Tuesday: Croagunk\n-Wednesday: Carnivine\n-Thursday: Croagunk\n-Friday: Skorupi\n-Saturday: Skorupi</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="241">Great Marsh Area 2\n \n-Sunday: Skorupi\n-Monday: Skorupi\n-Tuesday: Croagunk\n-Wednesday: Croagunk\n-Thursday: Carnivine\n-Friday: Croagunk\n-Saturday: Skorupi</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="242">Great Marsh Area 3\n \n-Sunday: Croagunk\n-Monday: Skorupi\n-Tuesday: Skorupi\n-Wednesday: Croagunk\n-Thursday: Croagunk\n-Friday: Carnivine\n-Saturday: Croagunk</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="243">Great Marsh Area 4\n \n-Sunday: Carnivine\n-Monday: Croagunk\n-Tuesday: Skorupi\n-Wednesday: Skorupi\n-Thursday: Croagunk\n-Friday: Croagunk\n-Saturday: Carnivine</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="244">Great Marsh Area 5\n \n-Sunday: Croagunk\n-Monday: Carnivine\n-Tuesday: Croagunk\n-Wednesday: Skorupi\n-Thursday: Skorupi\n-Friday: Croagunk\n-Saturday: Croagunk</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="2" table_id="245">Great Marsh Area 6\n \n-Sunday: Croagunk\n-Monday: Croagunk\n-Tuesday: Carnivine\n-Wednesday: Croagunk\n-Thursday: Skorupi\n-Friday: Skorupi\n-Saturday: Croagunk</string>
         <!--inside Marsh-->
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="3" table_id="538">Where would you like to go?</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="4" table_id="538">{00} didn't board the Quick Tram.</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="0" table_id="538">Ding-dong! Time's up!\nYour Safari Game is over.</string>
            <string block_id="0" entry_id="1" table_id="538">Ding-dong! You've run out of Safari Balls.\nYour Safari Game is over.</string>


</ds_strings_archive>