<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<strings is_override="0" is_primary="0" lang="en">
    <!--=Credits to SuperWorldSun for all strings-->
    <!--=SupersSpeedStrings Version-->

    <!--HMs in Hoenn-->
    <string id="271124538">{09}</string> <!--Use Rock Smash?-->
    <string id="271124780">{09}</string> <!--Use Strength?-->
    <string id="271003606">{09}</string> <!--Use Surf?-->
    <string id="271125480">{09}</string> <!--Use Dive? (Above)-->
    <string id="271125614">{09}</string> <!--Use Dive? (Bellow)-->
    <string id="271124270">{09}</string> <!--Use Cut??-->
    <string id="271125134">{09}</string> <!--HM Waterfall is active TODO double check if Ocarina is causing it-->
    <string id="271125187">{09}</string> <!--Use Waterfall?-->

    <!--Pokemon using an HM-->
    <string id="271124337">{09}</string>
    <string id="271125014">{09}</string> <!--Strength used-->

<!--Npcs-->
    <!--Gyms-->
        <!--Roxanne Battle-->
            <string id="270613551">{09}</string>
        <!--Roxanne End Battle-->
            <string id="270613753">\n\n</string>
        <!--Roxanne on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270612903">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8632]  /  +50%[$]  /  +75%[$]  /  +100%[$]\n \nSince you are so strong, you should challenge other GYM LEADERS.\nBy battling many TRAINERS, you should learn many things.</string>

        <!--Brawly Battle-->
            <string id="270521028">{09}</string>
        <!--Brawly End Battle-->
            <string id="270521191">\n\n</string>
        <!--Brawly on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270520845">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8736]  /  +50%[$13104]  /  +75%[$15288]  /  +100%[$17472]\n \nI can see your talent becoming a giant wave to cause a\nstorm of astonishment among TRAINERS one day!</string>

        <!--Wattson Battle-->
            <string id="270592423">{09}</string>
        <!--Wattson End Battle-->
            <string id="270592578">\n\n</string>
        <!--Wattson on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270592293">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8840]  /  +50%[$13260]  /  +75%[$15470]  /  +100%[$17680]\n \nWahahahah! Go forth and endeavor, youngster!</string>

        <!--Flannery Battle-->
            <string id="270530049">{09}</string>
        <!--Flannery End Battle-->
            <string id="270530207">\n\n</string>
        <!--Flannery on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270529862">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$8944]  /  +50%[$13416]  /  +75%[$15652]  /  +100%[$17888]\n \nYour power reminds me of someone... Oh! I know! You battle\nlike NORMAN, the GYM LEADER of PETALBURG.</string>

        <!--Norman Battle-->
            <string id="270562466">{09}</string>
        <!--Norman End Battle-->
            <string id="270562766">\n\n</string>
        <!--Norman on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270562807">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9048]  /  +50%[$13572]  /  +75%[$15834]  /  +100%[$18096]\n \nDAD: {01}...\nWhat is your dream? My dream... Hahaha...\nIt has already come true, actually.</string>

        <!--Winona Battle-->
            <string id="270627072">{09}</string>
        <!--Winona End Battle-->
            <string id="270627302">\n\n</string>
        <!--Winona on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270626929">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9152]  /  +50%[$13728]  /  +75%[$16016]  /  +100%[$18304]\n \nThough I fell to you, I will remain devoted to BIRD POKéMON.</string>

        <!--Tate & Liza Battle-->
            <string id="270671115">{09}</string>
        <!--Tate & Liza End Battle-->
            <string id="270671365">\n\n</string>
        <!--Tate & Liza on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270670621">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9256]  /  +50%[$13884]  /  +75%[$16198]  /  +100%[$18512]\n \nTATE: Looks like the bond between you and your POKéMON\nis far stronger than the bond that we share as twins.\nLIZA: You will become even stronger!\nWe've battled you, so we know.</string>

        <!--Juan Battle-->
            <string id="270686544">{09}</string>
        <!--Juan End Battle-->
            <string id="270686766">\n\n</string>
        <!--Juan on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270686072">[ON COOLDOWN / 18 Hours]\n[$9360]  /  +50%[$14040]  /  +75%[$16380]  /  +100%[$18720]\n \nThe TRAINERS who have gathered all the GYM BADGES of HOENN\nshould make way to the ultimate destination. The POKéMON\nLEAGUE. Travel to the easternmost reaches of HOENN, to the\nisland EVER GRANDE. There, you shall find the POKéMON\nLEAGUE.</string>

    <!--Elite Four-->
        <!--Door Guard-->
            <string id="270702312">{09}</string>
            <string id="270702575">{09}</string>

        <!--Sidney Battle-->
            <string id="270696359">{09}</string>
        <!--Sidney End Battle-->
            <string id="270696610">\n\n</string>
        <!--Sidney on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270696684">{09}</string>

        <!--Phoebe Battle-->
            <string id="270696974">{09}</string>
        <!--Phoebe End Battle-->
            <string id="270697253">\n\n</string>
        <!--Phoebe on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270697283">{09}</string>

        <!--Glacia Battle-->
            <string id="270697644">{09}</string>
        <!--Glacia End Battle-->
            <string id="270697908">\n\n</string>
        <!--Glacia on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270698048">{09}</string>

        <!--Drake Battle-->
            <string id="270698302">{09}</string>
        <!--Drake End Battle-->
            <string id="270698645">\n\n</string>
        <!--Drake on Cooldown-->
            <string id="270698672">{09}</string>

        <!--Wallace Battle-->
            <string id="270699596">{09}</string>
        <!--Wallace End Battle-->
            <string id="270700204">\n\n</string>
        <!--Wallace Beat-->
            <string id="270700390">{09}</string>
        <!--May-->
            <string id="270700746">{09}</string>
            <string id="270700811">{09}</string>
        <!--Brendan-->
            <string id="270700882">{09}</string>
            <string id="270700962">{09}</string>
        <!--Prof. Birch-->
            <string id="270701030">{09}</string>
            <string id="271213373">{09}</string>
            <string id="271211820">{09}</string>
            <string id="270701389">{09}</string>
        <!--Wallace-->
            <string id="270701465">{09}</string>
            <string id="270701547">{09}</string>
        <!--May-->
            <string id="270701689">{09}</string>
        <!--Brendan-->
            <string id="270701813">{09}</string>
        <!--Wallace-->
            <string id="270702862">{09}</string>
            <string id="270703011">{09}</string>

        <!--Battle Frontier-->
            <!--Battle Tower-->
                <!--All clerks within battle areas-->
                    <string id="270793991">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270794043">{09}</string>
                <!--First clerk-->
                    <string id="270796087">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270796211">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270796710">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270794791">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270795019">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270796268">The BATTLE TOWER's SINGLE BATTLE ROOMS are facilities for\nconducting SINGLE BATTLES with three POKéMON. There are\nmany SINGLE BATTLE ROOMS in the BATTLE TOWER for team\nbattles. In each of the SINGLE BATTLE ROOMS, seven TRAINERS\nawait your challenge. If you manage to defeat all seven, you\nwill earn Battle Points. If you want to interrupt your challenge,\nplease save the game. If you don't save before interrupting,\nyou will be disqualified.</string>
                <!--Second clerk-->
                    <string id="270796770">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270796894">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270797392">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270795227">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270795453">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270796951">The BATTLE TOWER's DOUBLE BATTLE ROOMS are facilities for\nconducting DOUBLE BATTLES with four POKéMON. There are\nmany DOUBLE BATTLE ROOMS in the BATTLE TOWER for team\nbattles. In each of the DOUBLE BATTLE ROOMS, seven TRAINERS\nawait your challenge. If you manage to defeat all seven, you\nwill earn Battle Points. If you want to interrupt your challenge,\nplease save the game. If you don't save before interrupting,\nyou will be disqualified.</string>
                <!--Third clerk-->
                    <string id="270797451">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270797574">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270798299">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270795659">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270795883">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270797630">The BATTLE TOWER's MULTI BATTLE ROOMS are facilities for\nconducting MULTI BATTLES. For MULTI BATTLES, you must\npartner with a TRAINER in the TOWER and enter with two\nPOKéMON each. Inside the TOWER is a room named the\nBATTLE SALON where you may meet other TRAINERS. There,\nyou must find a TRAINER to act as your partner in MULTI\nBATTLES. Once you have partnered up, you will be shown to a\nMULTI BATTLE ROOM. In the MULTI BATTLE ROOM, seven tag\nteams await your challenge. If you manage to defeat all seven\nteams, you will earn Battle Points. If you want to interrupt\nyour challenge, please save the game. If you don't save\nbefore interrupting, you will be disqualified.</string>
                <!--Fourth clerk-->
                    <string id="270798357">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270798485">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270799424">The LINK MULTI BATTLE ROOM challenge is only for two\nlinked players.</string>
                    <string id="270798546">The BATTLE TOWER's MULTI BATTLE ROOMS are facilities for\nconducting MULTI BATTLES with a friend. You must link with\nyour friend. You must partner with your friend and enter two\ndifferent kinds of POKéMON. There are many MULTI BATTLE\nROOMS in the BATTLE TOWER for team battles. In a MULTI\nBATTLE ROOM, seven tag teams await you and your friend to\nmake a tag-team challenge. If you manage to defeat all seven\nteams, you will earn Battle Points. Please beware that unlike\nother ROOMS, you may not interrupt your challenge. Once you\nstart, you must battle seven MULTI BATTLES in a row nonstop.</string>
                <!--Left info board-->
                    <string id="270800262">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270800531">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270800759">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270801022">The LINK MULTI BATTLE Mode is for two friends to mount a\nchallenge together. You and your friend must be linked together.\nYou must choose two POKéMON at the registration counter.\nThese POKéMON must be different from those of your friend.\nYou may not interrupt this challenge in the middle,\nunlike other modes.</string>
            <!--Battle Factory-->
                    <string id="270901704">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270896105">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270896069">{09}</string>
            <!--First Clerk-->
                    <string id="270895342">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270895482">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270895539">The Battle Swap Single Tournament is a SINGLE BATTLE\ncompetition using only rental POKéMON. First, you will be\nloaned three POKéMON specifically for this event. Using the\nsupplied rental POKéMON,you must conduct a SINGLE BATTLE.\nIf you win, you are permitted to trade one of your rental\nPOKéMON. Repeat this cycle of battling and trading if you win\nseven times in a row, you will earn Battle Points. If you want to\ninterrupt your challenge, please save the game. If you don't save,\nyou will be disqualified from your challenge.</string>
                    <string id="270896327">Thank you for participating! I will return your\nPOKéMON in exchange for our rental POKéMON.\nI must also save the event results. Please wait.</string>
                <!--Second Clerk-->
                    <string id="270897043">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270897183">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270897240">The Battle Swap Double Tournament is a DOUBLE BATTLE\ncompetition using only rental POKéMON. First, you will be\nloaned three POKéMON specifically for this event. Using the\nsupplied rental POKéMON, you must conduct a DOUBLE BATTLE.\nIf you win, you are permitted to trade one of your rental\nPOKéMON. Repeat this cycle of battling and trading if you win\nseven times in a row, you will earn Battle Points. If you want to\ninterrupt your challenge, please save the game. If you don't\nsave before interrupting, you will be disqualified.</string>
                <!--Center Info Board-->
                    <string id="270899046">In a Battle Swap event, you may use only three POKéMON.\nWhether you are renting or swapping, your team may not\nhave two or more of the same POKéMON.</string>
                    <string id="270899195">You may swap POKéMON only with the TRAINER you have just\ndefeated. You may swap for only those POKéMON used by the\nbeaten TRAINER.</string>
                    <string id="270899326">After every battle you win, you may swap for one of your\ndefeated opponent's POKéMON. You will not be able to swap\nPOKéMON with the seventh TRAINER in the event.</string>
                    <string id="270899488">There are two key points to be aware of when swapping\nPOKéMON. First, when swapping, you can't check the stats\nof the POKéMON you are about to receive. Second, the\nPOKéMON on your team are lined up in sequence, depending\non the order in which you rented them. This sequence\nremains unchanged even when swaps are made.</string>
                    <string id="270899806">In the Open Level, the rental POKéMON and the opposing\nTRAINERS' POKéMON are all Level 100.</string>
            <!--Battle Pike-->
                <!--Left Info Board-->
                    <string id="270911044">The BAG and POKéNAV may not be used during a Battle\nChoice challenge.</string>
                    <string id="270911114">During a Battle Choice challenge, any BERRY or HERB\nheld by POKéMON will be effective only once.</string>
                    <string id="270911211">During a Battle Choice challenge, the sequence of POKéMON\ncannot be changed. The sequence must be set before starting\nyour challenge.</string>
            <!--Battle Palace-->
                <!--Both Clerks-->
                    <string id="270852312">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270852377">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270853017">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270852467">Sigh... You do not have the three POKéMON required for the\nchallenge. To enter, you must provide three different kinds of\nPOKéMON. These POKéMON must all be of Level 50 or lower.\nThey also must not be holding the same kinds of items. EGGS{02}\nineligible. Come back when you have made your preparations.</string>
                    <string id="270852766">Sigh... You do not have the three POKéMON required for the\nchallenge. To enter, you must provide three different kinds of\nPOKéMON. They also must not be holding the same kinds of\nitems. EGGS{02} ineligible. Come back when you have made your\npreparations.</string>
                <!--First Clerk-->
                    <string id="270851419">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270851607">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270851553">{09}</string>
                <!--First Clerk-->
                    <string id="270854918">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270855106">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270855052">{09}</string>
                <!--Center Info Board-->
                    <string id="270856107">Here, POKéMON are required to think and battle by themselves.\nUnlike in the wild, POKéMON that live with people behave\ndifferently depending on their nature.</string>
                    <string id="270856265">Depending on its nature, a POKéMON may prefer to attack no\nmatter what. Another POKéMON may prefer to protect itself from\nany harm. Yet another may enjoy vexing or confounding its foes.\nDue to its nature, a POKéMON will have favorite moves that it is\ngood at using. It may also dislike certain moves that it has\ntrouble using.</string>
                    <string id="270856592">There are offensive moves that inflict direct damage on the\nfoe. There are defensive moves that are used to prepare for\nenemy attacks or used to heal HP and so on. There are also\nother somewhat-odd moves that may enfeeble the foes with\nstat problems including poison and paralysis. POKéMON will\nconsider using moves in these three categories.</string>
                    <string id="270856936">When not under command by its TRAINER, a POKéMON may be\nunable to effectively use certain moves. A POKéMON is not good\nat using any move that it dislikes. If a POKéMON only knows\nmoves that do not match its nature, it will often be unable\nto live up to its potential.</string>
                    <string id="270857204">Depending on its nature, a POKéMON may start using moves\nthat don't match its nature when it is in trouble. If a POKéMON\nbegins behaving oddly in a pinch, watch it carefully.</string>

            <!--Battle Arena-->
                <!--Battle Clerk-->
                    <string id="270885222">{09}</string>
    <string id="270885452">In the BATTLE ARENA, we undertake the Set KO Tourney. All\nparticipants enter with a team of three POKéMON. The three\nPOKéMON must be lined up in the order in which they are to\nappear. During battle, the POKéMON will appear one at a\ntime in the preset order. Once a POKéMON enters battle, it must\nremain out until the match is decided. If a match remains\nundecided in three turns, it goes to judging. If you wish to\ninterrupt your challenge, please save the game. If you don't\nsave, you will not be able to continue with your challenge.\nIf you pull off the feat of beating seven TRAINERS in succession,\nwe will present you with Battle Points.</string>
                    <string id="270886163">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270885354">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270886259">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270886568">My dear challenger! You do not have the three POKéMON\nrequired for entry. To qualify, you must bring three different\nkinds of POKéMON. The three different POKéMON must all be\nLevel 50 or lower. They also must not hold the same kinds\nof items. EGGS{02} ineligible. When you have made your\npreparations, please do return.</string>
                    <string id="270886309">My dear challenger! You do not have the three POKéMON\nrequired for entry. To qualify, you must bring three different\nkinds of POKéMON. They also must not hold the same kinds of\nitems. EGGS{02} ineligible. When you have made your preparations,\nplease do return.</string>
                    <string id="270885407">{09}</string>
                <!--Left Info Board-->
                    <string id="270888450">The Set KO Tourney has special rules, unlike standard battles.\nFirst, one battle lasts only three turns. If the outcome is not\ndecided after three turns, it goes to judging. The REFEREE will\nchoose the winner based on how the POKéMON battled.\nAlso, a POKéMON cannot be switched out until its battle's\noutcome is decided.</string>
                    <string id="270888771">The first judging factor is «Mind.»\nThis factor evaluates how aggressive the battlers were.\nThe judging is based on how often the TRAINERS ordered\nthe use of offensive moves.</string>
                    <string id="270888946">The second judging factor is «Skill.»\nThis factor evaluates how effectively POKéMON moves were\nused. If a move worked successfully, the Skill rating goes up.\nIf a move failed, the Skill rating is lowered. If it was an offensive\nmove, the Skill rating goes up if the move was «super effective»\nand goes down if it was «not very effective.» The Skill rating will\nnot go up for moves such as PROTECT and DETECT. If the\nopponent used PROTECT or DETECT, and your POKéMON\nfailed to hit with a move, its Skill rating will not go down.</string>
                    <string id="270889474">The third judging factor is «Body.»\nThis factor is based on how much HP remained at the end of a\nbattle. The rating takes into account how much HP a POKéMON\nhad at the start of battle, and what remained at the end.</string>


            <!--Battle Frontier Shop-->
                <!--Store clerk-->
                    <string id="270923770">{09}</string>
                    <string id="270925586">{09}</string>

        <!--Nurse Joy-->
            <!--Healing from NJ-->
                <string id="271001323">{09}</string>
            <!--Waiting...-->
                <string id="271002048">{09}</string>
            <!--Thanks for waiting-->
                <string id="271001496">{09}</string>
            <!--Come again-->
                <string id="271001563">{09}</string>

            <!--Breeder end text-->
            <string id="271131670">{09}</string>

        <!--Pokemart Store-->
                <string id="271002145">{09}</string>
                <string id="271002175">{09}</string>

        <!--Ash Collector-->
        <string id="270988298">{09}</string>
        <string id="270988506">{09}</string>
        <string id="270988611">A {02}, huff-puff?\nThere's not enough ash here to make that, though, huff-puff.\nLet's see... {03} is the number of steps you'll need to walk\nthrough volcanic ash for me to make that item, huff-puff.\nWhich item would you rather have me make instead, huff-puff?</string>

        <!--Bike Shop-->
        <!--RYDEL (Bike Shop)-->
            <string id="270594555">{09}</string> <!--Switch Bikes?-->
            <string id="270594607">{09}</string> <!--Bike Switched-->
            <string id="270594659">The MACH BIKE was exchanged for an ACRO BIKE!\n[Use the ACRO BIKE to Hop across gaps and ledges!]</string>
            <string id="270594708">The ACRO BIKE was exchanged for a MACH BIKE!\n[Use the MACH BIKE to Speed across Cracked floors\nand go up slopes!]</string>
            <string id="270594756">{09}</string> <!--Ending convo-->
            <string id="270594493">{09}</string> <!--Ending convo-->
    <!--Bike Shop HandBook-->
        <!--MACH BIKE HandBook-->
            <string id="270595141">It's a handbook on the MACH BIKE.\nWhich page do you want to read?</string>
            <string id="270595207">A BIKE moves in the direction that the + Control Pad is pressed.\nIt will speed up once it gets rolling.\nTo stop, release the + Control Pad.\nThe BIKE will slow to a stop.\n \nWant to read a different page?</string>
            <string id="270595408">Press + Control Pad in the direction you want to go.\n \nWant to read a different page?</string>
            <string id="270595610">There are small sandy slopes throughout the HOENN region.\nThe loose, crumbly sand makes it impossible to climb normally.\nBut if you have a MACH BIKE, you can zip up a sandy slope.\n \nWant to read a different page?</string>
        <!--ACRO BIKE HandBook-->
            <string id="270595821">It's a handbook on the ACRO BIKE.\nWhich page do you want to read?</string>
            <string id="270595887">The Page is torn out...\n[This function isn't possible]\n \nWant to read a different page?</string> <!--Wheelies-->
            <string id="270596085">Keeping the B Button pressed, your BIKE can hop on the spot.\nThis technique is called a bunny hop.\nYou can ride while hopping, too.\n \nWant to read a different page?</string> <!--B hops-->
            <string id="270596248">The Page is torn out...\n[This function isn't possible]\n \nWant to read a different page?</string> <!--Jump-->


    <!--Safari-->
        <!--Left Clerk-->
            <string id="271208308">$500?</string>
            <string id="271208475">{09}</string>
            <string id="271208502">{09}</string>
            <string id="271208530">{09}</string>
            <string id="271208559">{09}</string>
            <string id="271208407">{09}</string>
        <!--Right Clerk-->
            <string id="271208097">{09}</string>
        <!--Outside safari door helper-->
            <string id="271209131">{09}</string>
            <string id="271208916">You still have time left.\nWould you like to exit the SAFARI ZONE now?</string>
            <string id="271208986">{09}</string>
            <string id="271209032">{09}</string>


    <!--Contest hall-->
        <!--Left Clerk-->
            <string id="271035815">Hello!\nThis is the reception counter for\nPOKéMON CONTESTS.\nOh? It appears that you don't have a POKéBLOCK CASE yet.\nIn that case, we need to provide you with this!</string>
            <string id="271036072">{09}</string>
        <!--Right Clerk-->
            <string id="16780410">Did you know you can enter a contest with up to three\nother friends? Just link up with them before you sign up!</string>

    <!--Mt Chimney-->
        <!--Meteorite Machine-->
            <string id="270728978">A METEORITE is fitted on a mysterious machine...\nDo you want to remove the METEORITE?</string>
            <string id="270729062">{01} removed the METEORITE from\nthe mysterious machine.</string>
            <string id="270729116">{01} left the METEORITE where it was.</string>
            <string id="270729152">This mysterious machine...\nIt makes no response whatsoever.</string>

    <!--Norman's Gym Doors-->
        <string id="270561822">{09}</string>
        <string id="270561920">{09}</string>
        <string id="270561979">{09}</string>
        <string id="270562039">{09}</string>
        <string id="270562097">{09}</string>
        <string id="270562156">{09}</string>
        <string id="270562215">{09}</string>
        <string id="270562276">{09}</string>

</strings>